( Birds chirping )
( Quacks )
( Horn honks )
Hello , Cassie ! Hiya , girl . Hello there .
Now , let 's see .
Looks like Mari 's getting cards from half the civilized world .
Mari Collingwood .
Mari Collingwood . Mari Collingwood .
You 'd think she 's the only kid to reach the age of 17 .
Of course , she is about the prettiest piece I 've ever seen .
( Estelle ) Mari Collingwood , you hurry up !
Okay , Okay -
Drill sergeant .
( I DAVID HESS : " The Road Leads to Nowhere " )
Did you call the repair service ?
Mmm-hmm .
Did you tell them I was a physician and had to have a phone ?
No , actually , I told them you were an international bookie
and I was 1O months pregnant with quintuplets .
Hey , what 's new in the outside world ?
Same old stuff , murder and mayhem .
( John ) What 's for dinner tonight ?
( Estelle ) Freezer 's full , take your choice .
What 's that supposed to mean ? Mari , I want you to be careful tonight .
Your mother tells me the place you 're going is in a bad neighborhood .
I will , Daddy .
No bra ?
Of course not ! Nobody wears those anymore .
Nobody except us drill sergeants .
Yeah , but look , Estelle . You can see her nipples as plain as day .
Daddy , don 't be so clinical .
But it 's immodest .
Then I 'll get some sandpaper !
Look , younglady , when I was your age ...
When you were my age , you all wore brassieres
that made your tits stick out like torpedoes .
Tits ! What 's this " tits " business ? Sounds like I 'm back in the barracks .
All right , then . Mammary glands .
They used to tie them up like little lunatics in straitjackets
- and they stuffed socks in their bras . - Mari !
You told me that yourself , Mother .
If God had meant women to go around
with their busts exposed , Mari Collingwood ,
he wouldn 't have given us clothes !
Who are you gonna see tonight ?
- Bloodlust . - Bloodlust ?
Yeah , Bloodlust . What 's wrong with them ?
I was just reading about them .
Aren 't they the guys that dismember live chickens during their act ?
They only did that once , Daddy .
Don 't you feel sorry for the chicken ?
Oh , Daddy , I couldn 't tell you the nights I cried myself to sleep
over that chicken .
( Mari ) Hey , have you seen the car keys ?
On the table .
I think it 's crazy .
What 's crazy ?
All that blood and violence .
I thought you were supposed to be the love generation .
Hey , that reminds me .
What ?
Here 's a little something for you .
Just a gift to tide you over till tomorrow .
Oh , Daddy !
Daddy .
Oh , Mother . It 's nice .
Well , maybe it 'll bring you luck .
By the way , who are you going out with tonight ? Anyone we know ?
Well , Phyllis Stone .
Phyllis Stone ?
But , yeah ... I know you don 't like her , Mother ,
but I 'm safe with her . She comes from that neighborhood .
What neighborhood ?
Where the concert is . You know , from that slum .
I 'm sure she does .
( Phyllis ) Come on ! I got something for us .
What ?
Come on . You 'll see .
- Okay . Oh ! - Hurry up _
( John ) ' Who 's Phyllis Stone ?
' You make her sound like the bride of Frankenstein . '
( Estelle ) ' She 's the girl that takes care of the horses
' down the Johnson place , isn 't she , Mari ? '
( Mari ) ' What worries you ? '
( Estelle ) ' From what Nancy Springer tells me ,
' that 's not all she takes care of down there . '
Mari tells me you 're from Manhattan . What does your father do ?
( Phyllis ) ' Oh , my parents are in the iron and steel business . '
( Estelle ) Iron and steel , both together . How unusual .
Yeah , well , my mother irons , and my father steals .
( Phyllis ) ' Come on , Mari . '
( Phyllis ) I wish we had some decent grass .
- ( Mari ) Yeah , it 'd be nice to get stoned . - ( Phyllis ) You don 't have any , do you , Mari ?
- ( Mari ) No ! Of course not . Me ? - ( Phyllis ) Maybe we can get some before the concert .
( Mari ) Yeah , the concert .
( Phyllis ) I wonder what it would be like to make it with Bloodlust .
It would just be really soft . Like in a whole bunch of cotton .
You know what I mean ?
- Cotton ? - No ! Soft and gentle .
- Oh , give me a break ! - Really sensitive , not wild and gory .
God !
- You 're too much , man . Cotton ! - No .
It 's Bloodlust , man ! Like , they 're crazy !
Like cotton candy , you know .
( I DAVID HESS : " Wait for the Rain " )
( Mari ) The leaves are beautiful .
Yep ! They 're really starting to change . I guess winter 's coming on .
Yep . Hey , I changed . I changed this winter .
What do you mean , you changed ?
I mean , my breasts filled out .
Yeah , didn 't you notice ? Look .
I mean , they were nothing last summer .
I didn 't know you last summer .
I know . Well , they have .
Well , congratulations !
Come on . I feel like a woman for the first time in my life .
Yeah ?
Rodney Johnson !
( Giggles )
( I Slow music playing on radio )
( Changing radio stations )
( I DAVID HESS : " The Road Leads to Nowhere " )
( Phyllis exclaiming )
( Mari ) You 're crazy !
( Radio announcer ) ' The police have already spread their dragnet over a five-state area
' in their effort to apprehend the fugitives ... '
- ( Mari ) ' Far out ! This is gorgeous . ' - ( Radio announcer ) ' According to reliable sources ... '
( Changing radio stations )
( Mari ) ' Leave that on , Phyllis . I want to hear it . '
( Changing radio station )
( Radio announcer ) ' The daring daylight escape of the two convicted murderers ,
' dope pushers and rapists cost the lives of two prison guards
' and surprisingly , the life of a German shepherd .
' According to eyewitness reports , the animal ,
' which was sent after the two fleeing men , was kicked to death
' by a young , animal-like woman who leaped from the getaway car .
' The alleged driver of the car was Junior Stillo .
' Junior Stillo is the illegitimate son of the leader of the two escapees ,
' Krug Stillo , who was serving a life sentence for the 1966 triple slaying
' of a priest and two nuns .
' Krug Stillo is reputed to have hooked his own son on heroin
' to control the youngster 's life .
' The man is armed and considered extremely dangerous .
' The second escaped convict is identified as Fred " Weasel " Podowski ,
' who has a long police record for child molesting , peeping Tom-ism
' and assault with a deadly weapon .
' The three men were accompanied in their getaway by an unknown woman
' described only as young , strong and animal-like .
' Police believe the four may still be in the New York City area
' but expect them to try to leave the state within the next 48 hours . '
Thanks . Sounds like good advice .
( Sadie ) # I 'm singin ' in the rain #
Sadie !
- Yeah ? - Hurry up out of there !
I want to take a bath , too .
Okay , okay ! Hey , what do you think of your new clothes ?
I handpicked them at K0rvette 's .
Wonderful .
( Knocking on door )
( D09 barks )
- Who is it ? - ( Man ) It 's J. Edgar Hoover .
- Any trouble ? - No .
Where 's Sadie ?
( Fred ) Taking a bath .
( Sadie ) Hey , is Junior back yet ?
Yeah , and I 'm here , too .
( Sadie ) Send him in with my beer , okay ?
You heard her .
Go to the icebox and get a beer . There 's a lady in there , man .
( Fan whirring )
( Whirring stops )
( Sadie humming )
Here 's your beer , Sadie .
( Sadie ) There he is , the man of the hour .
Thank you .
You glad your old man 's out of the clink ?
Yeah , sure .
You know , it 's really a shame you don 't get along better with Krug .
You got to change your head around .
Become someone else altogether .
I 've been thinking about names and everything .
How does " Agatha Greenwood " grab you ?
Like something out of Brighter Day .
Yeah , you 're probably right .
What do you want to be ?
- A frog . - You look like a frog .
If I was a frog , I 'd have my own lily pad .
I could sit there all day long , just ...
( imitates frog )
I could do that , man , and nobody would bother me .
I could watch the flies .
( imitating fly buzzing )
( Gulps )
( Croaks )
( Laughs raucously )
- ( Fred ) Better watch him , Krug ! - Hey .
Leave Sadie alone , you little toad , or I 'll squash you flat as a lily pad .
- ( Mari ) Do we have time before the concert ? - ( Phyllis ) Sure , don 't worry about it .
Goodie ! I want to have at least two scoops .
I know exactly what I 'm going to have . Mint chocolate chip .
- A mint chocolate chip ? - Yeah .
No , I don 't like that .
( Mari ) What 's this yellow stuff right here ?
Lemon sherbet .
Sherbet . I don 't want sherbet .
Oh , can I taste yours ?
Make your own . What do you want ?
I don 't want that . I want ... What else do you have ?
( Man ) Banana Royal , Neapolitan , Maple Walnut , Tutti-Frutti ...
- Nut ! - Nuts for the nut .
Big goon , put me down !
I hate you !
( Sadie grunts )
( Sadie ) Let me up .
Hey , forget it ! You got the cream of American manhood here .
The cream of American manhood . That 's good , Krug !
Shut up ! And get away from my woman .
Your woman ? I thought she was our woman .
Just a minute ! Buzz off ! I 'm not neither of yours woman .
I am my own frigging woman !
- She 's right , Krug . - ( Krug ) You shut up !
Hey , what have you been doing ?
Reading them creep women lib magazines while I was up in the jug ?
Maybe .
Why don 't you just lay back and enjoy being inferior ?
Zoom off ! You male chauvinist dog !
- Pig , Sadie . - What ?
Male chauvinist pig .
Okay , you male chauvinist pig !
- She 's right , Krug . - ( Krug ) You shut up !
I ain 't putting out anymore until I get a couple of more chicks around here .
Couple of more chicks ?
Yeah . Equal representation .
- What , are you crazy ? - She 's right , Krug .
Get out of here !
God ! This neighborhood 's awful . It 's so dirty . My mother was right .
Come on , it 's not awful , it 's just funky . That 's all .
Dirt all over the place .
Keep your eyes open for someone who might be dealing .
( Both chuckle )
Yeah .
- ( Phyllis ) Want me to ask him ? - ( Mari ) Yeah . Go ahead .
Hey , man .
You don 't know where we could score on some good grass , do you ?
- Nah , I don 't know that stuff . - Thanks .
- Bummer . - Come on .
Oh , man ! Hey , hey , lady ! Come on back here .
Let 's get together .
( Phyllis ) Yeah ?
I do happen to have in my possession
an extra ounce of good stuff .
Oh yeah , what kind ?
Colombian .
- Colombian ? - Yeah .
Far out !
- How much ? - $ 20 .
$ 20 , and it 's Colombian ?
Yeah , well , you know , I need the money , but if that 's too high ...
No , no , no ! That 's great . We 'll take it . How do we get it ?
Oh , uh ...
This is my roommate , Sam .
Hiya , girls !
This is my sister , Martha .
Martha , these girls , you know , want to buy some grass .
Come on in . Come on in .
- Gotcha ! - Oh , shit !
Hey , stick around a while . How about a bite ?
Yeah , I 'd like a little something to eat myself .
Nice going , junkie . Here 's your yum-yums .
- So much for him . - Now , I don 't want you girls to worry .
I mean , we just wanted some company . That 's all , you know .
No , it wasn 't that expensive at all .
Looks good .
( Sighs )
This room belongs in a magazine .
Not bad , if I do say so . Hmm .
( Bell rings )
I feel like a bridegroom . I 'm hearing bells .
( Chuckles )
I have a cake in the oven . Come on .
A cake ?
You wanted some grass ?
What do you want with some grass ?
Hey , you guys ain 't cows , is ya ?
Little cows looking for some grass ?
Let me hear you moo . Come on .
( Mooing )
Yeah , but they got some cute little udders on them .
You guys let us the hell out of here , or I 'm going to start screaming !
( Mooing )
Hey , you gonna scream ?
Listen .
Let me give you a little bit of free advice .
If you make one peep ...
( I Upbeat music playing )
( Estelle ) Cockeyed as hell .
John , I should have bought one at the bakery .
They had such pretty ones there .
( John ) Nonsense . It 's truly remarkable .
Come on in the living room .
I want to attack you .
Listen . Why don 't you guys let us go ?
We know you were just kidding around .
- Oh , yes . - We 'll split ,
and we won 't say anything to anybody , I swear .
You must think we 're pretty stupid .
No .
We ain 't stupid .
We might be
horny old pigs ,
but we ain 't stupid .
Get your hands away , Sadie .
Come on , Krug . I had her first . Please .
I said get your hands away , bitch !
Chicken breast .
( Mari ) Phyllis !
Do that again , and you 're dead .
Easy , Weasel .
We don 't want to off somebody the first night out .
I mean ,
it 'd be a shame to get this floor all messed up with blood .
Be so messy .
You see ,
there are other ways to do things .
( Exclaims )
( Phyllis groans )
( Phyllis ) No !
Stop it .
No . No .
( Phyllis groans )
( Fred laughs evilly )
Castle 's ready . Here 's to the princess .
To the princess !
To her queen .
( Rooster crowing )
Come on !
( Krug ) Okay , sweetheart , I 'll put you right on top of your friend here .
( Sadie ) Take it easy , you could hurt ' em .
( Krug ) They 're okay .
Okay , the both of you settle down , you got a long ride ahead .
I 'm outta here .
( Engine starts )
( Estelle ) Yes .
- ( Sheriff on phone ) ' It 's pretty common , you know ? ' - ( Estelle ) Yes , I understand .
' Sure she hasn 't called ? '
No , she hasn 't .
' Well , sorry I couldn 't have been of more help . '
Why , thank you very much . You 're very kind .
- Goodbye . - ' Goodbye . '
Nothing ?
The theater manager said that concert was over at 2 : 00 this morning .
Well , it 's dawn now .
We 'll wait an hour , then we 'll call the police .
Come on ! Things are not that bad . At least we have our phone again .
She 's all right .
Staying out all night , well , it 's classic .
It 's a kid 's way of saying she 's grown up .
It 's that damn Phyllis Stone 's fault .
All right , don 't , Estelle ! Now , she 'll come home .
Let her have a fling .
Taking them girls , you know , that 's the kind of crime
people never forgive you for .
A sex crime .
Shut up , Weasel ! You 're disturbing my rhythm .
How would you do this sex crime business , anyway ?
My brother Sol , the plumber , he makes twice as much money as me
and gets three weeks vacation , too .
Shut up , shithead !
You think the cops is closing in on us ?
I don 't know , I just got this feeling at the back of my neck .
Maybe you got crabs .
( J ' DAVID HESS : " Sadie and Krug ( Baddies ' Theme ) " )
( Fred ) Sex crime !
I wonder what the meanest , foulest , rottenest ,
raunchiest sex crime ever was .
Hey , Sadie ! What do you think the sex crime of the century was ?
Oh , shit !
Hey , I 'm serious !
I ought to kill you .
How ' bout the Boston Strangler ? I always admired him .
- Bush league ! - I got it !
- You sure ? - Yeah ! Frood !
- Frood ? - Sigmund Frood !
Do you remember when a telephone pole was just a telephone pole ?
Yeah .
Not anymore , sweetheart .
It 's a giant puh-hay-lis .
- Puh-hay-lis ? - Puh-hay-lis ?
I can 't even look at the Grand Canyon anymore without crossing my legs .
It 's bullshit .
This icing is delicious .
You must get a lot of hysterical parents calling you now , huh , Sheriff ?
Well , it 's not that unusual , Mrs. Collingwood .
( John ) Oh ?
No , we 've been getting a lot of calls like this
in the past three or four years .
Kids running off to the big city for a few days .
Now , chances are that Mari will be back before supper .
Still , it 's wise of you to call us , Dr. Collingwood .
At least all our phones are working .
That 's just great !
We 're a million miles from nowhere , too ! King car of the road !
All right , what 's the matter ?
It stopped !
Hey , I think I found the trouble .
This thing pulled out , and it 's all covered with oil .
Christ , didn 't they teach you nothing in reform school ?
Take it easy on him , he 's just a kid .
I know , but when I was his age , I could fix any car in two seconds .
You schmuck .
( Sadie groans )
( Fred ) Hey , Krug , where the hell are we ?
I just have the strangest feeling we should be doing something more .
Now , hold on , Mrs. Collingwood .
Now Harry , my deputy Harry , he 's down there in the radio car .
He 's calling New York right now .
And if we hear anything ... Here he is right now .
( Knocks )
( Sheriff ) : What did you hear , Harry ?
New York police say they don 't have anybody
answering Mari 's description in jail or on ice .
- ( Sheriff ) : Harry ... - It 's their term .
Guy in the morgue says he hasn 't had a kid on ice all day .
First time in five years .
Is that the last of the cake ?
There 's a tool kit in the trunk . I want you to start this goddamn car .
( Screams )
Bitch ! She bit me !
Krug , this ain 't getting us out of the state .
She bit me ! That bitch bit me !
Weasel , we 're gonna have a little fun .
- ( Fred ) Krug . - ( Krug ) Car 's on the blink , Weasel .
( Sadie ) No , Krug .
( Krug ) As long as we got you brats along ...
( Sadie ) What are you gonna do ?
( Krug ) We ain 't going to be able to call a mechanic , go to a gas station ,
nothing .
( Sheriff ) : We 'll get the phone company hustling on the service
so we can get a call from her .
It 'll be all right .
You know , kids get ants in their pants sometimes .
She 's just letting off a little steam .
Come on , there !
( Mari crying )
Dig these crazy woods , man .
( Shushing )
Come on , Junior . Come on .
Come on . Move it .
( Krug ) Let 's go to the right , down by the water .
( Junior ) All right .
( Sheriff ) : Who do you suppose that is ?
( Deputy ) I don 't recognize it .
Looks like someone got stuck . Want to go out , have a look ?
( Sheriff ) : No , no . Come on , let 's go , kid . We got more important things to do .
That ain 't going to find us Mari Collingwood .
Weasel , take out your knife .
( Chuckles )
( Krug ) Now I 'm gonna tell this little lady here to do something .
And if she doesn 't do exactly what I tell her to ,
I want you to cut her ...
I want you to cut her friend .
( Sadie ) Oh , brother !
- ( Krug ) Untie ' em . Untie ' em . - Come on .
- Hey . - He 's talking to you .
Come here .
Piss your pants .
( Fred laughs )
( Sadie ) Piss your pants !
I said , piss your pants .
You sick mother ...
( Mari screams )
( Mari ) Phyllis , he cut me .
Piss your pants .
( Sadie ) Do it !
( Fred ) Watch her pee .
She 's doing it .
( All laugh )
Look at that !
( Sadie ) Oh , God ! Hell !
( Fred ) That 's beautiful .
Now , take ' em off .
( Krug ) I said , take ' em off !
( Sadie ) You 're so sick !
( Sadie ) Oh , yeah ! Take ' em off !
I told you about her .
( Fred ) She 's got lovely legs .
( Sadie ) This is really a riot , man ! I dig it !
Take ' em off ! Take it all off .
( Fred ) She got her little panties all stained .
Can we get Weasel a pair of those pants ?
Do you want a pair of those pants , Weasel ?
How about some with a couple of hearts on them ?
( Fred laughs )
( Sadie ) She 's got a good-looking ass on her .
Come on , we 're going to play . Up we go .
Hit her .
Hard !
Sock it to her , baby .
I said , hit her .
( Phyllis ) I 'm sorry , I 'm sorry , Mari .
Hit her in the stomach with all your might .
Stop it ! Stop it !
You 're gonna kill someone if you 're not careful .
What the hell are you doing ?
Oh , shit !
You guys got to be crazy , man .
If you 're not careful , you 're gonna kill someone .
Make them make it with each other , man !
That 's a good idea !
Make them make it with each other .
( Sadie ) Too sick , man .
Loosen her up a little bit . Wait a minute .
Oh , baby , don 't ... Come on , sweetheart . Don 't worry about it .
( Krug ) You 'll have plenty of time to feel the pain .
You know , Weasel here is a specialist with a twist .
( Sadie ) Do it !
( Mari gasps )
( Krug laughs )
Get it off !
( Phyllis ) Leave her alone !
( KFUg ) Come on .
- We got to do it . - I can 't .
I can 't . I can 't .
560s )
I know , it 's sick . I know .
It 's okay . I know .
It 's sick . But it 's okay .
It 's just you and me here . Nobody else . Just you and me , okay ?
( Krug ) Do it .
( Phyllis ) It 's okay .
( Sadie ) It 's all right . We 're not going to hurt you .
( Phyllis ) You already hurt her !
What do you think you 're doing ?
( Sheriff ) : No , Doc Collingwood , still no word on Mari .
But we 'll let you know just as soon as we hear something .
Yes , sir . Yes , sir .
Yes .
Well , I 'm glad you got your phone fixed .
Yeah , Doc , now you just stick right by that phone
' cause she might call , you know .
( John ) ' I 'm holding you personally responsible . '
Yes , sir .
' Call me if anything comes up . '
Yeah , okay .
- ' Goodbye . ' - Bye .
Hot damn , I wish I was something else sometimes .
You mean , like a duck or something ?
No , you damn fool ! I mean something else besides being a policeman .
Doc Collingwood again , huh ?
Doc Collingwood .
I bet she shacked up with Wilbur Cranshaw .
That shows how much you know ,
' cause Wilbur 's gone up to Coopersburg with Sweet Lily .
Who the hell is Sweet Lily ?
Well , it 's his pig .
He went up to Coopersburg . He 's gonna enter her in some fair up there .
Wilbur always was a little strange .
I remember he left town real sudden once before .
Just before his collie came down with a litter of pups .
I 'm going up to the car
to see if I can find something to cut some firewood with .
Firewood ?
Yeah , you know , you know , heat things up a little bit .
Oh , yeah .
You can handle things while I 'm gone , can 't you ?
Oh , sure .
( Mari crying )
Hey , listen , I 'm really cold .
Do you think it 'd be okay if I just put on my clothes ?
Just till Krug comes back . I 'm really cold .
Okay ?
Sure . Go ahead .
( Mari continues crying )
( Whispers ) Listen , I 'm gonna make a run for it .
When they go after me , you go and get help , okay ?
0K8 ) ' -
( Phyllis ) Okay .
( Fred ) ( Laughs ) You want to play ? Junior !
Watch that other girl . Don 't let nothing happen to her .
( Fred ) I 'm going to get you !
( Fred panting )
Man , I got to give up cigarettes .
- Shut up ! - Junior ? Is that your real name ?
I told you to shut up , or I 'll slap you silly .
I 'm gonna give you another name .
I 'm gonna give you another name . I 'm gonna call you Willow .
- Willow . Willow . - Willow .
Because you 're kind of beautiful , and you shake when the wind blows .
- Krug is the wind . - Let me alone .
Krug 's gonna really be pissed off we lost her .
Split up , okay ? Go that way .
You bitch ! Slow down !
Willow , do you have a girlfriend ?
Sure , I got lots of girlfriends just waiting to get me .
I don 't think you do .
No , you 're right .
I want to give you something .
I don 't want that .
- It 's worth a lot . See ? - I don 't want it .
I want to be your friend .
You want to get free .
- I want to be your friend . - ( Fred ) Sadie , where 'd she go ?
I want to be your friend . I can get you a fix .
Yeah .
You can get me a fix ?
Yeah , you 'd like that .
- Yeah . I 'd like it . - ( Fred ) Sadie ! Over there !
My father , he works with addicts . He 's got it in his house .
It 's here . I can get you methadone .
I can get you methadone , just as quick as that .
Really ! Come on , let 's get out of here .
- What , are you crazy ? - I live over there .
I live across the street . Come on , please !
- I can 't leave ! - Please .
- Krug will kill me . - No , not if you 're not here .
Screw , creep !
Son of a bitch .
( Man on radio ) ' Attention all townships . Attention all townships .
' We got a late bulletin on the fugitives
' Krug Stillo and Weasel Podowski and their two accomplices .
' State police got a filling station attendant down in Riverdale ,
' says he gassed them up and gave them directions to Corrington . '
Hey , they 're up our way !
' These guys might be coming our way , heading for Canada .
' Once again , description of that escape vehicle as follows .
' Dark green 1958 Cadillac convertible
' bearing license plate number E2546 .
' Repeat , Edna 25 ... '
How long does it take to get to the Collingwoods ' ?
- About 25 minutes . - Make it 15 .
( Engine starts )
( Siren wails )
( Phyllis ) Oh , God .
If you would just relax , listen , I can help you . I 'll get you out of this .
You stupid dyke !
( Fred ) Sadie !
I 'm gonna kill you .
You all right , Sadie ?
Yeah , I 'm okay . Let me up .
( Sadie ) Come on ! There she is !
( Panting )
( Exclaims )
I 'm gonna kill that bitch .
( Gasps )
( Grunting )
- ( Krug ) Feel better now ? - ( Fred ) Yeah , I 'm okay .
( Krug ) How did she get so close to the road ?
( Fred ) She threw some dirt in my face .
We caught her , though . What are you worried about ?
( Engine stalling )
( Deputy ) Goddamn car stopped .
You 're out of gas , you idiot !
Out of gas ?
God damn !
See ? I told you she wasn 't going far .
( Chuckles )
How 's your back , baby ?
( Screaming in pain )
( Screaming )
- ( Mari ) Phyllis ! Phyllis ! - ( Krug ) Oh , Christ .
Junior !
You said my name was Willow .
Willow , then !
You 've got to be a man and do something for once .
Mari , what would you do ? What would you do if you were me ?
Fuck !
( Mari ) Phyllis !
They 're coming after us .
Going somewhere ?
- Phyllis ? - Phyllis ?
Did she get away ?
( Mari screams )
- Take this , pigs ! - Get outta here . We hate cops !
God damn !
Damn hippies !
( Mari continues screaming )
What do you think , Weasel ?
 K-R-U-G
" Krug . " That 's really nice .
Oh , yeah .
( Krug ) You 're gonna get yours . You are really gonna get yours .
Little woolly .
( r DAVID HESS : " Now You 're All Alone " )
( Mari ) " Now I lay me down to sleep
" I pray the Lord my soul to keep
" if I shall die before I wake
" I pray the Lord my soul to take . "
( Gunshot )
( Barking )
Junior !
Go up to the car and get the suitcases .
Let 's get washed up and the hell out of here .
Yeah . Let 's do that .
Good grief , Frank . We 've been walking for nigh on an hour now .
It 's 7 : 00 and we 've still got a good 1O miles to go .
If you got any better ideas , Harry , you just come right out with them .
' Cause I can 't think of any other way to get from here to there
or any other place either , without riding or walking .
And since riding is out , thanks to you , you lamebrain you ,
then walking is the only thing that 's left .
Listen .
What ?
I hear something .
All I hear is you , you damn fool .
( Shushing )
Who the hell do you think you are ? Tonto ?
It 's a truck .
And some chickens , too .
Chickens ?
I only tell you what the road tells me .
Listen , Ada , we got a problem here . This is serious business .
Now we got to get to the Collingwood place right away .
Now , this is police business , and this is an emergency , you hear ?
Can you help us out ?
Have to ride on the roof .
On the roof ?
It 's the only place I have any room .
( Cackling )
Fasten your seatbelts !
Proceed , Ada .
Now , listen , Harry , if you tell any of the boys at the lodge about this ,
I 'm gonna fix your wagon .
( Engine starts )
God Sam !
What in thunder 's going on here , Ada ?
It 's got its maximum load .
I couldn 't get another chicken on here without it stalling .
And now I got you two on here , and you two ain 't chickens !
You mean this truck won 't start with us on it ?
You said it !
Listen , Ada , you 're gonna have to take some of those chickens
off that truck and let us on , you hear ?
How much do you weigh , Deputy ?
185.Why ?
How much you weigh , Sheriff ?
- About 180 . - Bullshit .
Well , maybe 190 . I don 't weigh myself every morning .
That 's 11 crates of chickens . And that ain 't hay .
Now look , Ada , you know I 'm a solemnly sworn officer of the law ?
Now , I got the law on my side , Ada .
And , Sheriff , I got the chickens and the truck !
( Fred ) Water ! Water !
You found water , chief .
( Krug ) Still got some in your eye .
( Fred ) Yeah ? You get it .
( Fred ) How 's that ? How 's that ?
Did I get everything ?
- Am I clean ? - Help me out of here . Come on .
- Am I clean ? - Yeah .
Atta girl !
( Krug ) Have a look , Sadie . ls my tie okay ?
( Sadie ) Beautiful , baby !
( KFUQ ) Yeah .
- ( Krug ) Gee , thanks ! - ( Sadie ) You 're welcome .
- ( Estelle ) John ! - I 'm in here !
We 've got guests .
I 'm sorry .
Guests ! Who is it ?
( Sadie exclaims )
Get your foot off the table !
( Sadie ) Being in this house makes me wish I was a lady .
This place is in the middle of nowhere , you know that ?
What are you doing with the Holy Bible ?
" Dearly beloved , we are gathered here ... "
( Shushing )
( Sadie ) Hey , Weasel , what are you doing ?
( Fred ) Nothing .
( John ) Who in the world is it ? I didn 't know anyone was coming over .
John , I want you to meet Harvey Wilson and his wife , Dorothy .
- How are you ? - Sam Hardy .
Sam .
- And Dave Rizalski . - David .
Do you know their car broke down right out front , John ?
Oh ? Anything serious ?
- Yeah , I 'm afraid we blew a rod . - ( John ) Oh , no .
Well , Willie 's Esso station is the only garage I know ,
and they close at 6 : 00 .
Well , it wouldn 't make any difference anyway .
The phone is still dead .
( Estelle ) They wanted us to drive them to a motel , but I said
that would be up to you ...
Mari still has the car .
It 's all right , we 've got plenty of room .
( Estelle ) Absolutely . Why , we have a perfectly good guest room .
And , well , there 's Mari 's room , I suppose .
Are you sure we 're not gonna put you folks to any trouble ?
Nonsense ! Our home is yours . Let me get your bags .
No , no , no ! Frank here is younger . He can handle it .
Well , why don 't I show you to your rooms ? Come on .
Fine .
Here , and through there . Okay ?
I 'll put some towels in the bathroom for you , and you can wash up if you like .
Bacon and eggs all right in the morning ?
- Thank you . - That 's marvelous .
Okay , well , we 'll be in the living room , and you can join us if you like .
Okay , just make yourselves comfortable .
Much obliged .
( Coughs )
Come on !
Very nice . Very nice .
The lady of the house is nice , too .
Hey , Krug , I want my fix , man .
( KFUQ ) Go jump !
~ Krug ? ' ( KWQ ) Yeah ?
Look at this .
What ?
Guess who lives here ?
( Chuckles )
I wonder what the odds are on that .
( Fred ) Couldn 't even tell you .
Feel like playing " Three Thirds of a Ghost " or something ?
How would you like me to put my boot up your ass sideways ?
I 'm sorry I don 't have anything better to offer you , but ...
It 's been such a confusing day .
Hell , you 've got a lotto offer .
I mean , this food is impeccable .
( Fred burps )
Are you folks on vacation ?
No . We 're sort of on a business trip .
What sort of business are you in ?
- Plumbing . - Insurance .
Well , which is it ?
You see , we 're actually in both .
We sell insurance to plumbing companies .
You know , in case they steal some toilets or something .
Yeah .
( Moaning )
( Mari ) Junior .
( Laughing )
' Stop it ! ' ( Screaming )
Stop it !
- ( Mari ) Willow ! - Stop it !
You 're gonna kill someone .
( Mari ) Willow .
( Groaning )
I 'm sorry .
You don 't mind if I smoke , do you ?
( JUFIiOr ) ( Screaming ) I 'm sorry !
I 'm sgmf !
( crying )
Shut up , you little creep ! I should 've killed you clown at the lake !
Shut up ! You 're worse than your goddamn mother !
You see , Dave upstairs , he lost one of our biggest accounts last week .
International Bathtub and Sink .
$ 500,000 account , down the drain , so to speak .
He kind of takes the blame on himself . Hasn 't got over it yet .
Any more spaghetti left ?
Goddamn high-class , tight-ass freakos .
All that goddamn silverware .
Who do they think they are , anyway ?
People in China eating with sticks ,
and these creeps got 16 utensils for every pea on the plate .
Take it easy .
It don 't make no matter , one way or the other .
Where 's that goddamn son of mine ?
He 's taking a piss , or something .
Did you get him his fix ?
Screw him .
( Coughing )
( Retching )
( Groans )
( Junior retching )
( Estelle ) ls there anything I can do in there ?
( Panting )
- Are you all right ? - Yeah .
Yeah , I 'm fine . I 'm fine .
Let me call my husband . He 's a doctor .
No , no , lady , please !
I 'm all right . I 'm all right .
( Gaspiflg )
Easy . Easy does it . You okay ?
( Krug ) What the hell have you been doing ?
( Junior ) Nothing .
( Junior ) Look , man ! I got to have a fix !
( Krug ) After breakfast .
- ( Junior ) Hey , Krug _ ' ( KFUQ ) Yeah ?
( Junior blowing nose )
( Junior ) I want my fix , man .
Look , man ! Cut it out !
- I got to have a fix ! - ( Krug ) Screw off .
( Junior ) Krug , we gotta get out of here ! If they find out we killed their kid ...
( Krug ) You shut up , or you 'll wind up in the lake with her !
( I DAVID HESS : " The Road Leads to Nowhere " )
- Oh , God , John . - Jesus Christ !
Isn 't there anything we can do for her ?
- Nothing . - John .
She 's dead .
0h , my baby !
Oh , baby .
( Estelle ) Don 't move . Open your mouth , please .
Don 't move .
Open your mouth , please .
- ( John ) Lights . - ( Estelle ) Lights .
- ( John ) Chisel . - ( Estelle ) Don 't move . Chisel .
Hammer .
Wider now .
Wider .
Don 't move .
No good .
( Clanking )
( Gasps )
Hello .
What are you doing up so late ?
Oh , uh ...
I thought I heard noises .
But it was just a dog in the garbage can outside .
I got a little hungry .
Thought I might raid the icebox .
Well , I must say , you ...
You do look like a man with a huge appetite .
I mean , all that spaghetti tonight and everything .
Yeah , that 's true .
Say , where 's your husband ?
I couldn 't help noticing that your room was empty .
Oh , he 's there .
He somehow finds me too hard to ...
- Well , he 's afraid of me . - You 're kidding .
Oh , no , I only wish I was .
I could make love to a looker like you with my hands tied behind my back .
Let 's go over to the couch .
No , no , no ! Not here .
John might hear us and come in .
Why don 't we go outside ?
Outside ?
Please .
I want you .
Let 's go outside .
You know , I 've always dreamed of a man who could take me easily .
Almost like you said ,
with your hands tied behind your back .
Baby , believe me , I can literally do that . I 'm so super .
God damn it .
Here .
Tie me up .
No , I couldn 't !
I thought it was just some girlish fantasy .
I know no man could do that .
I said , tie me up .
Well ...
Okay , now you just unzip me , and that 's all I 'll need you for .
0K8 ) ' -
You got it caught .
On your little thing ! How did I do that ?
- Shall I just give it a little yank ? - No !
No , no , don 't do that ! Just ease it down .
Nice and easy .
That 's it .
Poor little fellow .
It 's not little . You just scared it , that 's all . Just wait .
( Snoring )
( Thudding )
If you don 't watch it , I 'm gonna come .
Please come then , sweetie .
Don 't you want me to do you good and proper ?
You can do both , can 't you ?
Hell , yeah !
I can come five or six times if you want me to .
( Fred ) You bitch .
I think I 'm gonna come .
( Estelle ) Are you sure , my love ?
Sweet mama !
Here I come !
( Screaming )
( Moaning )
- What 's going on ? - I don 't know . Shut up .
Krug , it 's Weasel ! What the hell has happened to him ?
What 's the trouble , Doc ?
Shut your filthy mouth !
Now , take it easy , Doc . Don 't do anything I wouldn 't do .
( Gunshot )
( Thudding )
( Krug ) Put the lights on !
( Grunting )
( Panting )
Son of a bitch .
Boy .
You can do better than that , come on . Right here .
Come on , come on , right here .
Oh , boy , you 're almost as good as Sadie . Why don 't you get something to help you ?
Come on . Maybe one of the andirons or something , you know .
Let 's even up the odds .
Who 's this ? Hello , there . You remember me ?
( Grunts )
Come on , Doc .
We 're just playing games now . We 're just beginning .
And what did you do with Weasel ? What did you do with him ?
What 's your name , little angel ?
Mari . Mari .
She was a lot tougher than you were , Doc .
She took a while to kill .
She was really tough .
We had a hard time with her .
But you 're just a pussy !
A real pussy .
Come on now , Doc . You can do better than that .
Just a couple of more , Doc .
Maybe one more for me .
( John coughs )
( Gunshot )
( Krug ) What the hell are you doing ?
Oh , you wanna kill me .
( Junior ) I 'll do it .
Okay , well , let me help you .
I really will .
Now , I want you to hold the gun out , just like that , see ?
You see that little notch in the back ? That little bump in the front ?
I want you to kind of get them lined up . That 's right .
You 're not shaking that much . I know you can aim the gun .
Just get them lined up , and pull the trigger .
No .
Come on . Pull the trigger .
I 'm gonna kill you , Krug .
You always were a loser .
( KFUg ) Junior ,
I wanna talk to you .
Listen to Daddy . Come on .
Now , I want you to take the gun ,
then I want you to turn around
and I want you to put it in your mouth
and I want you to blow your brains out !
( Junior sniffles )
- ( Junior ) No ! - No . Not at me .
I want you to take the gun , and I want you to put it in your mouth
and I want you to blow your brains out !
( Junior ) No !
- Blow your brains out ! - No !
Blow your ...
( Gunshot )
( Chainsaw whirrs )
( Chainsaw whirring )
Sorry , Krug .
But I could only find one shell .
- You better get out of here ! - Sadie !
Get away from me !
( Both scream )
You 're not going to get away from me !
( Both screaming )
( Sadie ) Get off of me !
( Krug ) Let 's just get it over with !
( Exclaims )
( Screams )
John ! For God 's sake , don 't !
( Krug screams )
( Sighs )
( I DAVID HESS : " Sadie and Krug ( Baddies ' Theme ) " )